{
    "id": "857c4822ed5147d5b706da7ad55dcbac",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mr. Cross was always angry ………………. his friends and family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "231a48ff85a54ab38239f5e4d3b5586c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He shouted ……………….. his wife and children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "30d85e8a93b149b4a0cc4ce219dd5681"
        },
        {
            "question": "So, they stayed away ………………… him as far as possible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "97c97690a3bf45769e8f5580da429542"
        },
        {
            "question": "One day, Mr. Cross was busy writing a letter. Just then a fly buzzed ……………. through the open window.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f612ec332f7846b6bcee08339bb95501"
        },
        {
            "question": "He rushed ……………….. the fly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "away",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ac424e684c31472aa4a8b69daa340ad4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fly flew into the kitchen and settled …………….. a pot of honey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67239c7ab9f640dfaf7fecc7042cdd6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Cross was trembling ……………….. anger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1982e71eded34111abbb2d8ebe7ef58b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He picked up a rod and hit the fly heavily. But the fly was too quick …………….. Mr. Cross.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "788b95043d4c49c7bb38937696a6659e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wherever the fly went, Mr. Cross followed ………………. his ruler.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c497528a5b8441a7b865ff34487b45ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everything went crashing ……………….. the floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b840853338a4daeb0527da93ae56a1e"
        }
    ]
}